<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>期刊目录 | Ju丶Blog</title>
    <link>/tag/%E6%9C%9F%E5%88%8A%E7%9B%AE%E5%BD%95/</link>
      <atom:link href="/tag/%E6%9C%9F%E5%88%8A%E7%9B%AE%E5%BD%95/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>期刊目录</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>2020</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/share_logo.png</url>
      <title>期刊目录</title>
      <link>/tag/%E6%9C%9F%E5%88%8A%E7%9B%AE%E5%BD%95/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Economic Review, 2020, 110(11)</title>
      <link>/post/2020-11-02-aer_content_611/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2020-11-02-aer_content_611/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Seasonal Liquidity, Rural Labor Markets, and Agricultural Production&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; Rural economies in many developing countries are characterized by a lean season in the months preceding harvest, when farmers have depleted their cash and grain savings from the previous year. To identify the impacts of liquidity during the lean season, we offered subsidized loans in randomly selected villages in rural Zambia. Ninety-eight percent of households took up the loan. Loan eligibility led to increases in on-farm labor and agricultural output, driving up wages in local labor markets. Larger effects for poorer households suggest that liquidity constraints contribute to inequality in rural economies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20180607&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20180607&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 季节性流动性，农村劳动力市场和农业生产&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 许多发展中国家的农村经济特点是收割前的几个月是淡季，当时农民已经耗尽了上一年的现金和粮食储蓄。为了确定淡季期间流动性的影响，我们在赞比亚农村的随机选择的村庄提供了补贴贷款。 98％的家庭接受了贷款。贷款资格导致农场劳动力和农业产出增加，从而提高了当地劳动力市场的工资。对贫困家庭的更大影响表明，流动性限制加剧了农村经济的不平等。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Arrival of Young Talent: The Send-Down Movement and Rural Education in China&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; This paper estimates the effects on rural education of the send-down movement during the Cultural Revolution, when about 16 million urban youth were mandated to resettle in the countryside. Using a county-level dataset compiled from local gazetteers and population censuses, we show that greater exposure to the sent-down youths significantly increased rural children&amp;rsquo;s educational achievement. This positive effect diminished after the urban youth left the countryside in the late 1970s but never disappeared. Rural children who interacted with the sent-down youths were also more likely to pursue more-skilled occupations, marry later, and have smaller families than those who did not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20191414&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20191414&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 青年人才的到来：下乡运动与中国农村教育&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 本文估计了文化大革命期间下乡运动对农村教育的影响，当时大约有1600万城市青年被要求在农村定居。我们使用根据当地地名词典和人口普查编制的县级数据集，表明对下乡青年的更多接触显着提高了农村儿童的教育成绩。在城市青年在1970年代末离开农村但从未消失后，这种积极作用减弱了。与未成年青年互动的农村儿童也比未参加教育的年轻人更有可能从事技能更高的职业，结婚晚些，并且家庭较小。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Does Information Break the Political Resource Curse? Experimental Evidence from Mozambique&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; Natural resources can have a negative impact on the economy through corruption and civil conflict. This paper tests whether information can counteract this political resource curse. We implement a large-scale field experiment following the dissemination of information about a substantial natural gas discovery in Mozambique. We measure outcomes related to the behavior of citizens and local leaders through georeferenced conflict data, behavioral activities, lab-in-the-field experiments, and surveys. We find that information targeting citizens and their involvement in public deliberations increases local mobilization and decreases violence. By contrast, when information reaches only local leaders, it increases elite capture and rent-seeking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20190842&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20190842&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 信息会破坏政治资源的诅咒吗？莫桑比克的实验证据&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 自然资源可能通过腐败和内乱对经济产生负面影响。本文测试了信息是否可以抵消这种政治资源的诅咒。在传播有关莫桑比克大量天然气发现的信息之后，我们将进行大规模的现场试验。我们通过地理参考冲突数据，行为活动，实地实验室实验和调查来测量与公民和地方领导人的​​行为有关的结果。我们发现，针对公民及其参与公共讨论的信息增加了当地动员并减少了暴力。相比之下，当信息仅到达本地领导者时，它会增加精英捕获和寻租的能力。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Devotion and Development: Religiosity, Education, and Economic Progress in Nineteenth-Century France&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; This paper studies when religion can hamper diffusion of knowledge and economic development, and through which mechanism. I examine Catholicism in France during the Second Industrial Revolution (1870–1914). In this period, technology became skill-intensive, leading to the introduction of technical education in primary schools. I find that more religious locations had lower economic development after 1870. Schooling appears to be the key mechanism: more religious areas saw a slower adoption of the technical curriculum and a push for religious education. In turn, religious education was negatively associated with industrial development 10 to 15 years later, when schoolchildren entered the labor market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20191054&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20191054&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 奉献与发展：十九世纪法国的宗教，教育与经济进步&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 本文研究了宗教何时可以阻碍知识传播和经济发展，以及通过哪种机制。我考察了第二次工业革命（1870年至1914年）期间法国的天主教。在此期间，技术成为技能密集型，从而导致在小学引入技术教育。我发现，更多的宗教场所在1870年之后的经济发展速度较慢。学校教育似乎是关键机制：更多的宗教地区看到技术课程的采用较慢，并推动了宗教教育。反过来，当学童进入劳动力市场时，宗教教育与10至15年后的产业发展负相关。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Gambling over Public Opinion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; We consider bargaining environments in which public opinion provides leverage by making compromises costly. Two parties make initial demands, before knowing the public opinion. If deadlocked, they can bargain again after public opinion forms, but suffer reputation costs if they compromise, i.e., scale back their demands. We show that in equilibrium, parties may choose to make incompatible demands initially and gamble over public opinion even though one or both parties must bear a cost later. We characterize when deadlocks arise, and how this affects the welfare of the public in a representative two-party democracy compared to a direct democracy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20181495&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20181495&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 赌博舆论&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 我们考虑在讨价还价的环境中，舆论通过做出代价高昂的妥协来发挥影响力。在了解公众意见之前，两党提出了初步要求。如果陷入僵局，他们可以通过舆论形式再次讨价还价，但是如果他们妥协，即缩减需求，则会蒙受声誉损失。我们表明，在均衡状态下，即使当事一方或双方必须承担一定的费用后，当事方仍可能选择最初提出不相容的要求并在公众舆论中进行赌博。我们描述了何时出现僵局，以及与直接民主制相比，在具有代表性的两党制民主制中僵局如何影响公众的福利。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; From Extreme to Mainstream: The Erosion of Social Norms&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; Social norms, usually persistent, can change quickly when new public information arrives, such as a surprising election outcome. People may become more inclined to express views or take actions previously perceived as stigmatized and may judge others less negatively for doing so. We examine this possibility using two experiments. We first show via revealed preference experiments that Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s rise in popularity and eventual victory increased individuals&amp;rsquo; willingness to publicly express xenophobic views. We then show that individuals are sanctioned less negatively if they publicly expressed a xenophobic view in an environment where that view is more popular.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20171175&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20171175&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 从极端到主流：社会规范的侵蚀&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 通常持续存在的社会规范可以在新的公共信息到来后迅速改变，例如令人惊讶的选举结果。人们可能会更倾向于表达观点或采取以前被认为受到侮辱的行动，并可能因此而对他人进行负面评价。我们使用两个实验来检验这种可能性。我们首先通过揭示的偏好实验表明，唐纳德·特朗普的受欢迎程度上升以及最终的胜利提高了人们公开表达仇外心理的意愿。然后，我们表明，如果个人在较普遍的环境中公开表达仇外心理，则受到的制裁较少。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Small and Large Firms over the Business Cycle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; This paper uses new confidential Census data to revisit the relationship between firm size, cyclicality, and financial frictions. First, we find that large firms (the top 1 percent by size) are less cyclically sensitive than the rest. Second, high and rising concentration implies that the higher cyclicality of the bottom 99 percent of firms only has a modest impact on aggregate fluctuations. Third, differences in cyclicality are not simply explained by financing, and in fact appear largely unrelated to proxies for financial strength. We instead provide evidence for an alternative mechanism based on the industry scope of the very largest firms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20181499&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20181499&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 整个商业周期中的小型和大型公司&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 本文使用新的机密人口普查数据来重新研究企业规模，周期性和财务摩擦之间的关系。首先，我们发现大公司（规模排名前1％）比其他公司对周期性的敏感度低。其次，集中度高和上升意味着底部99％的公司较高的周期性只会对总体波动产生适度的影响。第三，周期性差异并不能简单地通过融资来解释，实际上似乎与财务实力的代理无关。相反，我们为基于最大公司的行业范围的替代机制提供了证据。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Does When You Die Depend on Where You Live? Evidence from Hurricane Katrina&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; We follow Medicare cohorts to estimate Hurricane Katrina&amp;rsquo;s long-run mortality effects on victims initially living in New Orleans. Including the initial shock, the hurricane improved eight-year survival by 2.07 percentage points. Migration to lower-mortality regions explains most of this survival increase. Those migrating to low-versus high-mortality regions look similar at baseline, but their subsequent mortality is 0.83–1.01 percentage points lower per percentage point reduction in local mortality, quantifying causal effects of place on mortality among this population. Migrants&amp;rsquo; mortality is also lower in destinations with healthier behaviors and higher incomes but is unrelated to local medical spending and quality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20181026&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20181026&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 死时是否取决于住所？来自卡特里娜飓风的证据&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 我们根据医疗保险队列估计了卡特里娜飓风对最初居住在新奥尔良的受害者的长期死亡影响。包括最初的冲击在内，飓风使八年生存期提高了2.07个百分点。迁移到低死亡率地区可以解释这种生存率的提高。那些迁移到低死亡率高死亡率地区的人群在基线时看起来很相似，但是其随后的死亡率每降低本地死亡率一个百分点，则降低0.83–1.01个百分点，从而量化了场所对这一人群死亡率的因果关系。行为健康的目的地和较高的收入目的地的移民死亡率也较低，但与当地医疗支出和质量无关。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Methods Matter: p-Hacking and Publication Bias in Causal Analysis in Economics&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; The credibility revolution in economics has promoted causal identification using randomized control trials (RCT), difference-in-differences (DID), instrumental variables (IV) and regression discontinuity design (RDD). Applying multiple approaches to over 21,000 hypothesis tests published in 25 leading economics journals, we find that the extent of p-hacking and publication bias varies greatly by method. IV (and to a lesser extent DID) are particularly problematic. We find no evidence that (i) papers published in the Top 5 journals are different to others; (ii) the journal &amp;ldquo;revise and resubmit&amp;rdquo; process mitigates the problem; (iii) things are improving through time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20190687&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20190687&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 方法很重要：经济学因果分析中的p-hacking和出版偏见&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 经济学上的信誉革命通过使用随机对照试验（RCT），差异差异（DID），工具变量（IV）和回归不连续性设计（RDD）促进了因果识别。将多种方法应用于25种主要经济学期刊上发表的21,000项假设检验中，我们发现p-hacking和出版偏见的程度因方法而异。 IV（在较小程度上是DID）尤其成问题。我们没有证据表明（i）前5种期刊上发表的论文与其他期刊不同； （ii）期刊的“修订和重新提交”程序减轻了该问题； （iii）随着时间的推移，情况正在改善。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; How Well Targeted Are Soda Taxes?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; Soda taxes aim to reduce excessive sugar consumption. We assess who is most impacted by soda taxes. We estimate demand using micro longitudinal data covering on-the-go purchases, and exploit the panel dimension to estimate individual-specific preferences. We relate these preferences and counterfactual predictions to individual characteristics and show that soda taxes are relatively effective at targeting the sugar intake of the young, are less successful at targeting the intake of those with high total dietary sugar, and are unlikely to be strongly regressive especially if consumers benefit from averted internalities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20171898&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20171898&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 苏打税的针对性如何？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 苏打水税旨在减少过多的食糖消耗。我们评估谁受苏打税影响最大。我们使用涵盖购买过程中的微观纵向数据来估计需求，并利用面板维度来估计特定于个人的偏好。我们将这些偏好和反事实预测与个人特征相关联，表明苏打税在针对年轻人的糖摄入量方面相对有效，在针对饮食中总糖含量高的人群中摄入较不成功，并且不太可能特别是强回归性消费者是否从避免的内部利益中受益。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Economic Review, 2020, 110(10)</title>
      <link>/post/2020-10-11-aer_content_607/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2020-10-11-aer_content_607/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Misperceived Social Norms: Women Working Outside the Home in Saudi Arabia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; We show that the vast majority of young married men in Saudi Arabia privately support women working outside the home (WWOH) and substantially underestimate support by other similar men. Correcting these beliefs increases men&amp;rsquo;s (costly) willingness to help their wives search for jobs. Months later, wives of men whose beliefs were corrected are more likely to have applied and interviewed for a job outside the home. In a recruitment experiment with a local company, randomly informing women about actual support for WWOH leads them to switch from an at-home temporary enumerator job to a higher-paying, outside-the-home version of the job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20180975&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20180975&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 误解的社会规范：沙特阿拉伯妇女在家外工作&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 我们表明，沙特阿拉伯的绝大部分年轻已婚男子私下为在外工作的妇女提供私人支持（WWOH），大大低估了其他类似男子的支持。纠正这些信念会增强男人（帮助他们的妻子寻找工作）的意愿（代价高昂）。几个月后，那些信念得到纠正的男人的妻子更有可能申请并面试外出工作。在与一家本地公司进行的招聘实验中，随机告知妇女有关WWOH的实际支持，这导致她们从在家中的临时调查员工作切换到薪水更高的家庭外工作。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Business-Cycle Anatomy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; We propose a new strategy for dissecting the macroeconomic time series, provide a template for the business-cycle propagation mechanism that best describes the data, and use its properties to appraise models of both the parsimonious and the medium-scale variety. Our findings support the existence of a main business-cycle driver but rule out the following candidates for this role: technology or other shocks that map to TFP movements; news about future productivity; and inflationary demand shocks of the textbook type. Models aimed at accommodating demand-driven cycles without a strict reliance on nominal rigidity appear promising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20181174&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20181174&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 商业周期解剖&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 我们提出了一种剖析宏观经济时间序列的新策略，为最能描述数据的商业周期传播机制提供模板，并利用其属性来评估简约和中等规模的模型。我们的发现支持存在主要的商业周期驱动因素，但排除了以下候选者的角色：与TFP运动相对应的技术或其他冲击；有关未来生产力的新闻；和教科书类型的通货膨胀需求冲击。旨在在不严格依赖名义刚性的情况下适应需求驱动的周期的模型似乎很有希望。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Patronage and Selection in Public Sector Organizations&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; In all modern bureaucracies, politicians retain some discretion in public employment decisions, which may lead to frictions in the selection process if political connections substitute for individual competence. Relying on detailed matched employer-employee data on the universe of public employees in Brazil over 1997–2014, and on a regression discontinuity design in close electoral races, we establish three main findings. First, political connections are a key and quantitatively large determinant of employment in public organizations, for both bureaucrats and frontline providers. Second, patronage is an important mechanism behind this result. Third, political considerations lead to the selection of less competent individuals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20181491&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20181491&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 公共部门组织的赞助和Selection选&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 在所有现代官僚机构中，政客在公共就业决策中保留一定的酌处权，如果政治联系代替个人能力，这可能会导致选拔过程中的摩擦。依靠1997-2014年间巴西公共雇员的详细匹配雇主-雇员数据，以及在紧密选举中的回归不连续性设计，我们得出了三个主要发现。首先，对于官僚和一线提供者而言，政治联系是公共组织中就业的关键且数量上很大的决定因素。其次，光顾是这一结果背后的重要机制。第三，政治上的考虑导致选择能力较弱的个人。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Liquidity versus Wealth in Household Debt Obligations: Evidence from Housing Policy in the Great Recession&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; We exploit variation in mortgage modifications to disentangle the impact of reducing long-term obligations with no change in short-term payments (&amp;ldquo;wealth&amp;rdquo;), and reducing short-term payments with no change in long-term obligations (&amp;ldquo;liquidity&amp;rdquo;). Using regression discontinuity and difference-in-differences research designs with administrative data measuring default and consumption, we find that principal reductions that increase wealth without affecting liquidity have no effect, while maturity extensions that increase only liquidity have large effects. This suggests that liquidity drives default and consumption decisions for borrowers in our sample and that distressed debt restructurings can be redesigned with substantial gains to borrowers, lenders, and taxpayers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20181243&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20181243&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 家庭债务负担中的流动性与财富：大衰退中住房政策的证据&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 我们利用抵押贷款修改中的变化来消除减少长期债务而不改变短期付款（“财富”）和减少短期付款而不改变长期债务（“流动性”）的影响。使用回归不连续性和差异差研究设计以及管理违约和消费的行政数据，我们发现增加财富而不影响流动性的本金减少没有影响，而仅增加流动性的期限延长具有很大影响。这表明在我们的样本中，流动性驱动着借款人的违约和消费决策，不良的债务重组可以重新设计，从而为借款人，贷方和纳税人带来可观的收益。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Importing Political Polarization? The Electoral Consequences of Rising Trade Exposure&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; Has rising import competition contributed to the polarization of US politics? Analyzing multiple measures of political expression and results of  congressional and presidential elections spanning the period 2000 through 2016, we find strong though not definitive evidence of an  ideological realignment in trade-exposed local labor markets that commences prior to the divisive 2016 US presidential election. Exploiting the  exogenous component of rising import competition by China, we find that trade exposed electoral districts simultaneously exhibit growing  ideological polarization in some domains, meaning expanding support for both strong-left and strong-right views, and pure rightward shifts in  others. Specifically, trade-impacted commuting zones or districts saw an increasing market share for the Fox News channel (a rightward shift),  stronger ideological polarization in campaign contributions (a polarized shift), and a relative rise in the likelihood of electing a Republican to  Congress (a rightward shift). Trade-exposed counties with an initial majority White population became more likely to elect a GOP conservative,  while trade-exposed counties with an initial majority-minority population became more likely to elect a liberal Democrat, where in both sets of  counties, these gains came at the expense of moderate Democrats (a polarized shift). In presidential elections, counties with greater trade  exposure shifted toward the Republican candidate (a rightward shift). These results broadly support an emerging political economy literature  that connects adverse economic shocks to sharp ideological realignments that cleave along racial and ethnic lines and induce discrete shifts in  political preferences and economic policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20170011&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20170011&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 导入政治两极分化？贸易暴露增加的选举后果&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 进口竞争的加剧是否加剧了美国政治的两极化？通过分析从2000年到2016年的多种政治表达方式以及国会和总统大选的结果，我们发现，尽管有权威性的证据表明，在2016年美国总统大选之前，暴露于贸易的地方劳动力市场已经发生了意识形态上的调整。利用中国进口竞争加剧的外在因素，我们发现暴露于贸易的选举区在某些领域同时表现出日益加剧的意识形态两极分化，这意味着扩大了对左强和右强观点的支持，而在另一些领域则纯粹是右移。具体来说，受贸易影响的通勤区或地区的福克斯新闻频道市场份额不断增加（向右转移），竞选捐款中的意识形态两极化更加强烈（两极化转变），选举共和党参议员的可能性相对增加（向右移动）。最初拥有多数人口的贸易暴露县白人更有可能选举共和党，而最初拥有少数族裔人口的贸易暴露县更有可能选举一个自由民主党，在这两个县中，这些收益都是以牺牲温和的民主党人为代价（两极分化）。在总统选举中，贸易敞口较大的县向共和党候选人转移（向右转移）。这些结果在很大程度上支持了新兴的政治经济学文献，这些文献将不利的经济冲击与意识形态的重新整合联系在一起，这些重新排列的思想沿着种族和族裔路线分裂，并引发了政治偏好和经济政策的离散变化。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Sources of Inaction in Household Finance: Evidence from the Danish Mortgage Market&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; We build an empirical model to attribute delays in mortgage refinancing to psychological costs inhibiting refinancing until incentives are sufficiently strong; and behavior, potentially attributable to information-gathering costs, lowering the probability of household refinancing per unit time at any incentive. We estimate the model on administrative panel data from Denmark, where mortgage refinancing without cash-out is unconstrained. Middle-aged and wealthy households act as if they have high psychological refinancing costs; but older, poorer, and less-educated households refinance with lower probability irrespective of incentives, thereby achieving lower savings. We use the model to understand frictions in the mortgage channel of monetary policy transmission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20180865&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20180865&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 家庭财务不作为的根源：丹麦抵押市场的证据&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 我们建立了一个经验模型，将抵押贷款再融资的延迟归因于心理成本抑制了再融资，直到激励措施足够强大为止。行为和行为，可能归因于信息收集成本，从而在任何激励下均降低了单位时间内家庭再融资的可能性。我们根据丹麦的行政管理小组数据估算了该模型，该国没有抵押的抵押贷款再融资不受限制。中产阶级和富裕家庭的行为似乎使他们的心理再融资成本高昂；但是较老的，较贫穷的和受教育程度较低的家庭进行再融资的可能性较低，而与激励措施无关，从而实现了较低的储蓄。我们使用该模型来了解货币政策传导的抵押渠道中的摩擦。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Sources of Displaced Workers&amp;rsquo; Long-Term Earnings Losses&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; We estimate the magnitudes of reduced earnings, work hours, and wage rates of workers displaced during the Great Recession using linked employer-employee panel data from Washington state. Displaced workers&amp;rsquo; earnings losses occurred mainly because hourly wage rates dropped at the time of displacement and recovered sluggishly. Lost employer-specific premiums explain only 17 percent of these losses. Fully 70 percent of displaced workers moved to employers paying the same or higher wage premiums than the displacing employers, but these workers nevertheless suffered substantial wage rate losses. Loss of valuable specific worker-employer matches explains more than one-half of the wage losses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20180652&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20180652&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 流离失所工人长期收入损失的来源&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 我们使用华盛顿州的雇主-雇员面板数据估算了大萧条期间流离失所的工人的收入，工作时间和工资率下降的幅度。流离失所工人的收入损失主要是由于流离失所时的小时工资率下降而恢复缓慢。损失的雇主专用保费仅解释了这些损失的17％。完全有70％的流离失所工人转向雇主，支付的费用与取代雇主的工资相同或更高，但这些工人却遭受了可观的工资率损失。有价值的特定工雇主匹配的损失解释了一半以上的工资损失。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Artificial Intelligence, Algorithmic Pricing, and Collusion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; Increasingly, algorithms are supplanting human decision-makers in pricing goods and services. To analyze the possible consequences, we study experimentally the behavior of algorithms powered by Artificial Intelligence (Q-learning) in a workhorse oligopoly model of repeated price competition. We find that the algorithms consistently learn to charge supracompetitive prices, without communicating with one another. The high prices are sustained by collusive strategies with a finite phase of punishment followed by a gradual return to cooperation. This finding is robust to asymmetries in cost or demand, changes in the number of players, and various forms of uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20190623&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20190623&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 人工智能，算法定价和合谋&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 在定价商品和服务时，算法逐渐取代了人类决策者。为了分析可能的后果，我们在重复价格竞争的主力寡头模型中实验研究了由人工智能（Q学习）支持的算法的行为。我们发现，算法始终在学习彼此竞争的价格，而无需彼此沟通。串谋战略维持有限的惩罚，然后逐步恢复合作，从而维持了高价。这一发现对于成本或需求的不对称性，参与者数量的变化以及各种形式的不确定性具有鲁棒性。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Voter Turnout with Peer Punishment&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; We introduce a model where social norms of voting participation are strategically chosen by competing political parties and determine voters&amp;rsquo; turnout. Social norms must be enforced through costly peer monitoring and punishment. When the cost of enforcement of social norms is low, the larger party is always advantaged. Otherwise, in the spirit of Olson (1965), the smaller party may be advantaged. Our model shares features of the ethical voter model and it delivers novel and empirically relevant comparative statics results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20170476&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20170476&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 选民投票率与同伴处罚&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 我们介绍了一个模型，在该模型中，竞争性政党从战略上选择了投票参与的社会规范，并确定了选民的投票率。必须通过昂贵的同伴监视和惩罚来实施社会规范。当执行社会规范的成本很低时，较大的一方总是有优势的。否则，按照奥尔森（Olson，1965）的精神，较小的政党可能会占优势。我们的模型具有道德选民模型的特征，并且提供了新颖且与经验相关的比较静态结果。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Upping the Ante: The Equilibrium Effects of Unconditional Grants to Private Schools&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; We assess whether financing can help private schools, which now account for one-third of primary school enrollment in low- and middle-income countries. Our experiment allocated unconditional cash grants to either one (L) or all (H) private schools in a village. In both arms, enrollment and revenues increased, leading to above- market returns. However, test scores increased only in H schools, accompanied by higher fees, and a greater focus on teachers. We provide a model demonstrating that market forces can provide endogenous incentives to increase quality and increased financial saturation can be used to leverage competition, generating socially desirable outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20180924&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20180924&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 事前准备：私立学校无条件拨款的均衡效应&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 我们评估了融资是否可以帮助私立学校，私立学校目前占中低收入国家小学入学人数的三分之一。我们的实验向村庄中的一所（L）或所有（H）私立学校分配了无条件现金补助。在这两个方面，入学人数和收入均有所增加，带来了高于市场的回报。但是，考试成绩仅在H学校增加，伴随着更高的学费以及对教师的更多关注。我们提供了一个模型，证明市场力量可以提供内在的激励机制来提高质量，而增加的金融饱和度可以用来促进竞争，从而产生社会可取的结果。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Economic Review, 2020, 110(9)</title>
      <link>/post/2020-09-09-aer_content_604/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2020-09-09-aer_content_604/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Household Debt Revaluation and the Real Economy: Evidence from a Foreign Currency Debt Crisis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; We examine the consequences of a sudden increase in household debt burdens by exploiting variation in exposure to household foreign currency debt during Hungary&amp;rsquo;s late-2008 currency crisis. The revaluation of debt burdens causes higher default rates and a collapse in spending. These responses lead to a worse local recession, driven by a decline in local demand, and negative spillover effects on nearby borrowers without foreign currency debt. The estimates translate into an output multiplier on higher debt service of 1.67. The impact of debt revaluation is particularly severe when foreign currency debt is concentrated on household, rather than firm, balance sheets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20181585&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20181585&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 家庭债务重估与实体经济：来自外币债务危机的证据&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 我们通过利用匈牙利2008年末货币危机期间家庭外币债务敞口的变化来研究家庭债务负担突然增加的后果。债务负担的重估导致更高的违约率和支出崩溃。这些回应导致了当地需求下降的驱动，并导致了更严重的地方经济衰退，并对附近没有外币债务的借款人产生了负面的溢出效应。估计数转化为1.67的较高债务偿还率的产出乘数。当外币债务集中在家庭而不是公司的资产负债表上时，债务重估的影响尤其严重。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Rich Pickings? Risk, Return, and Skill in Household Wealth&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; We investigate wealth returns on an administrative panel containing the disaggregated balance sheets of Swedish residents. The expected return on household net wealth is strongly persistent, determined primarily by systematic risk, and increasing in net worth, exceeding the risk-free rate by the size of the equity premium for households in the top 0.01 percent. Idiosyncratic risk is transitory but generates substantial long-term dispersion in returns in top brackets. Systematic and idiosyncratic risk both drive the cross-sectional distribution of the geometric average return over a generation. Furthermore, wealth returns explain most of the historical increase in top wealth shares.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20170666&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20170666&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 丰富的采摘？家庭财富的风险，回报和技巧&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 我们在一个包含瑞典居民资产负债表的管理面板上调查财富收益。家庭净财富的预期回报率具有很强的持久性，主要由系统风险决定，其净资产也不断增加，超出无风险利率的比例超过了前0.01％的家庭的股权溢价规模。特质风险是暂时的，但会在高括号中的回报中产生长期的长期分散。系统风险和特质风险都驱动一代人的几何平均收益的横截面分布。此外，财富回报可以解释历史上最高财富份额的增长。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Overreaction in Macroeconomic Expectations&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; We study the rationality of individual and consensus forecasts of macroeconomic and financial variables using the methodology of Coibion and Gorodnichenko (2015), who examine predictability of forecast errors from forecast revisions. We find that individual forecasters typically overreact to news, while consensus forecasts underreact relative to full-information rational expectations. We reconcile these findings within a diagnostic expectations version of a dispersed information learning model. Structural estimation indicates that departures from Bayesian updating in the form of diagnostic overreaction capture important variation in forecast biases across different series, yielding a belief distortion parameter similar to estimates obtained in other settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20181219&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20181219&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 宏观经济预期过度反应&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 我们使用Coibion​​和Gorodnichenko（2015）的方法研究宏观经济和金融变量的单个预测和共识预测的合理性，他们从预测修订中检查了预测误差的可预测性。我们发现，个别预测人员通常对新闻反应过度，而共识预测相对于完整信息的理性预期则反应不足。我们在分散的信息学习模型的诊断期望版本中协调这些发现。结构估计表明，以诊断过度反应形式出现的贝叶斯更新偏离捕获了不同系列之间预测偏差的重要变化，从而产生了类似于其他设置中获得的估计的置信度失真参数。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Self-Fulfilling Debt Dilution: Maturity and Multiplicity in Debt Models&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; We establish that creditor beliefs regarding future borrowing can be self-fulfilling, leading to multiple equilibria with markedly different debt accumulation patterns. We characterize such indeterminacy in the Eaton-Gersovitz sovereign debt model augmented with long maturity bonds. Two necessary conditions for the multiplicity are (i) the government is more impatient than foreign creditors, and (ii) there are deadweight losses from default. The multiplicity is dynamic and stems from the self-fulfilling beliefs of how future creditors will price bonds; long maturity bonds are therefore a crucial component of the multiplicity. We introduce a third party with deep pockets to discuss the policy implications of this source of multiplicity and identify the potentially perverse consequences of traditional &amp;ldquo;lender of last resort&amp;rdquo; policies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20180831&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20180831&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 自我实现的债务稀释：债务模型的成熟度和多重性&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 我们确定，债权人对未来借款的信念可以自我实现，从而导致债务均衡模式明显不同的多重均衡。我们在具有长期债券的伊顿－格索维茨主权债务模型中确定了这种不确定性。多重性的两个必要条件是（i）政府比外国债权人更不耐烦，并且（ii）违约造成无谓损失。多样性是动态的，源于对未来债权人如何对债券定价的自我实现信念。因此，长期债券是多样性的重要组成部分。我们介绍了一个财大气粗的第三方来讨论这种多样性来源的政策含义，并确定传统“最后贷款人”政策的潜在不良后果。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Nonrivalry and the Economics of Data&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; Data is nonrival: a person&amp;rsquo;s location history, medical records, and driving data can be used by many firms simultaneously. Nonrivalry leads to increasing returns. As a result, there may be social gains to data being used broadly across firms, even in the presence of privacy considerations. Fearing creative destruction, firms may choose to hoard their data, leading to the inefficient use of nonrival data. Giving data property rights to consumers can generate allocations that are close to optimal. Consumers balance their concerns for privacy against the economic gains that come from selling data broadly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20191330&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20191330&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 非竞争性与数据经济学&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 数据是无与伦比的：一个人的位置历史，病历和行车数据可以同时被许多公司使用。非竞争性导致回报增加。结果，即使在存在隐私考虑的情况下，跨公司广泛使用的数据也可能会带来社会收益。由于害怕创造性破坏，公司可能会选择ho积数据，从而导致非竞争性数据的低效使用。将数据财产权授予消费者可以产生接近最佳的分配。消费者在隐私保护和广泛销售数据所带来的经济利益之间取得平衡。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; An Estimated Structural Model of Entrepreneurial Behavior&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; Using a rich panel of owner-operated New York dairy farms, we provide new evidence on entrepreneurial behavior. We formulate a dynamic model of farms facing uninsured risks and financial constraints. Farmers derive nonpecuniary benefits from operating their businesses. We estimate the model via simulated minimum distance, matching both production and financial data. We find that financial factors and nonpecuniary benefits are of first-order importance. Collateral constraints and liquidity restrictions inhibit borrowing and the accumulation of capital, especially among high-productivity firms seeking to expand. The nonpecuniary benefits to farming are large and keep small, low-productivity farms in business. Although farmers are risk averse, eliminating uninsured production risk has only modest effects on capital and output.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20170370&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20170370&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 企业家行为的估计结构模型&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 通过由业主经营的纽约奶牛场组成的丰富小组，我们提供了有关企业家行为的新证据。我们建立了一个面临未保险风险和财务约束的农场动态模型。农民从经营企业中获得非金钱利益。我们通过模拟的最小距离估算模型，同时匹配生产和财务数据。我们发现，财务因素和非金钱利益至关重要。抵押限制和流动性限制会抑制借贷和资本积累，特别是在寻求扩张的高生产率公司中。农业的非金钱利益是巨大的，并且使小型，低生产率的农场经营。尽管农民不愿承担风险，但消除未保险的生产风险仅对资本和产出产生适度的影响。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Policy Language and Information Effects in the Early Days of Federal Reserve Forward Guidance&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; I show that the nature of the Federal Open Market Committee&amp;rsquo;s (FOMC&amp;rsquo;s) forward guidance language shapes the private sector&amp;rsquo;s responses to monetary policy statements. From February 2000 to June 2003, the FOMC only gave forward guidance about economic outlook risks, and a decrease in the expected federal funds rate path caused stock prices to fall, GDP growth forecasts to fall, and the unemployment rate to rise. From August 2003 to May 2006, the FOMC added forward guidance about policy inclinations, and a decrease in the expected federal funds rate path had the opposite effects. These results suggest that forward guidance that emphasizes economic outlook risks causes stronger information effects than forward guidance that emphasizes policy inclinations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20181721&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20181721&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 美联储早期指导中的政策语言和信息影响&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 我表明，联邦公开市场委员会（FOMC）前瞻性指导语言的性质决定了私营部门对货币政策声明的回应。从2000年2月至2003年6月，联邦公开市场委员会仅就经济前景风险给出了指导，而预期联邦基金利率路径的下降导致股价下跌，GDP增长预期下降以及失业率上升。从2003年8月到2006年5月，联邦公开市场委员会增加了有关政策倾向性的前瞻性指导，而预期联邦基金利率路径的下降则产生了相反的效果。这些结果表明，强调经济前景风险的前瞻性指南比强调政策倾向的前瞻性指南具有更强的信息效果。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Job Matching under Constraints&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; Studying job matching in a Kelso-Crawford framework, we consider arbitrary constraints imposed on sets of doctors that a hospital can hire. We characterize all constraints that preserve the substitutes condition (for all revenue functions that satisfy the substitutes condition), a critical condition on hospitals&amp;rsquo; revenue functions for well-behaved competitive equilibria. A constraint preserves the substitutes condition if and only if it is a &amp;ldquo;generalized interval constraint,&amp;rdquo; which specifies the minimum and maximum numbers of hired doctors, forces some hires, and forbids others. Additionally, &amp;ldquo;generalized polyhedral constraints&amp;rdquo; are precisely those that preserve the substitutes condition for all &amp;ldquo;group separable&amp;rdquo; revenue functions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20190780&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20190780&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 约束条件下的工作匹配&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 在凯尔索·克劳福德（Kelso-Crawford）框架下研究工作匹配，我们认为医院可以雇用的医生受到任意约束。我们描述了保留替代条件的所有约束条件（对于满足替代条件的所有收入函数），这是医院的收入函数实现良好竞争均衡的关键条件。当且仅当约束条件是“通用间隔约束条件”时，约束条件才保留替代条件，该条件指定了聘用医生的最小和最大人数，强迫某些聘用而禁止其他聘用。另外，“广义多面体约束”恰好是那些为所有“组可分离”收入函数保留替代条件的约束。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Ultimatum Bargaining with Rational Inattention&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; A seller bargains with a rationally inattentive buyer (Sims 2003) over a good of random quality. After observing quality, the seller makes a take-it-or-leave-it offer. The buyer pays attention to the seller&amp;rsquo;s product and offer at a cost proportional to expected entropy reduction. Because attention is free off-path, multiple equilibria emerge, many of which are efficient. A trembling-hand-like refinement (Selten 1975) rules out efficiency, delivering complete disagreement when attention is expensive and a unique equilibrium with trade when attention is cheap. In this equilibrium, the buyer overpays for low-quality goods, underpays for high-quality goods, and earns a strictly positive payoff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20170620&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20170620&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 最后通Bar讨价还价，注意力不集中&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 卖方与随机购买的商品在价格上与理性的购买者讨价还价（Sims，2003年）。观察质量后，卖方提出接受或保留的要约。买方关注卖方的产品，并以与预期的熵降低成正比的价格进行报价。由于注意力不受束缚，因此出现了多个平衡点，其中许多平衡点都是有效的。颤抖之类的提炼（Selten 1975）排除了效率，当注意力集中时，完全无法达成共识，而注意力廉价时，则与贸易形成独特的平衡。在这种平衡下，购买者为低品质商品多付了钱，为优质商品少付了钱，并获得了严格的正收益。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Two-Way Fixed Effects Estimators with Heterogeneous Treatment Effects&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; Linear regressions with period and group fixed effects are widely used to estimate treatment effects. We show that they estimate weighted sums of the average treatment effects (ATE) in each group and period, with weights that may be negative. Due to the negative weights, the linear regression coefficient may for instance be negative while all the ATEs are positive. We propose another estimator that solves this issue. In the two applications we revisit, it is significantly different from the linear regression estimator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/aer.20181169&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;10.1257/aer.20181169&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标题：&lt;/strong&gt; 具有异质处理效果的双向固定效果估计器&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; 具有周期和组固定效应的线性回归被广泛用于估计治疗效果。我们表明，他们估计每个组和每个时期的平均治疗效果（ATE）的加权总和，其权重可能为负。由于权重为负，因此线性回归系数可能会为负，而所有ATE均为正。我们提出了另一个估计器来解决这个问题。在我们再次访问的两个应用中，它与线性回归估计器有很大不同。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
